Nothing but loud on a lonely road
Just trying to get back to you I'm
carrying this heavy load They're telling me
what I have to do
The lights are bright, the stage is cold They're
trying to fit me in their mold I see your face
across the black I
know that we can find our way back We're worlds
apart, but our hearts beat the same.
I can hear you call my name. Through the
distance, through the static and the dark,
we're finding a way back to the start. Even when
we're worlds apart
They want the loudest They want the engine A
different version for a different show But
we're the ones who'll be hearing these
We've got a fire they'll never know We're worlds
apart But our hearts beat the same
I can hear you call my name Through the distance
Through the static and the dark We're finding a
way back to the start Even when we're worlds
apart
And when
the mountains fall And when the oceans rise I'll
find you I'll find you We're worlds apart, but
our hearts beat the same I
can hear you call my name Through the distance,
through the static and the dark We're finding
our way back to the start Even when we're worlds
apart world's apart and still